Tag! You're it!
标签！就是你了！
Oh, yeah? You're it!
哦，是吗？就是你了！
Excuse me! Genius at work here!
打扰一下！天才在这里工作！
Oh, my golly!
哦，天哪！
My painting!
It's ruined.
我的画！
它被毁了。
You turned my beautiful
self-portrait into a...
你让我变得美丽
自画像变成...
a sponge-blob!
一团海绵！
I think it looks good.
我觉得看起来不错。
What do you know, plebeian?
你知道什么，平民？
This is going where it belongs.
这将去往它所属的地方。
In the trash.
在垃圾桶里。
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
哇，哇，哇。
What have we here?
我们这里有什么？
Fellas, check this out.
伙计们，看看这个。
I've never seen
such a profoundly
我从未见过
如此深刻
beautiful work of art.
美丽的艺术品。
Huh, it reminds me
that in this chaotic world
呵呵，这让我想起了
在这个混乱的世界里
there is still unabashed beauty.
依然有不掩饰的美丽。
See? People love your painting.
看？人们喜欢你的画。
They're garbage people,
of course they like garbage.
他们都是垃圾人
他们当然喜欢垃圾。
For your information,
供你参考，
we all got art degrees
from Whale University.
我们都获得了艺术学位
来自鲸鱼大学。
Oh, be still,
my beating heart!
哦，安静点，
我跳动的心！
Who's responsible
for this masterpiece?
谁负责
为了这部杰作？
I'm Peggy Grouperheim,
big-time art dealer.
我是佩吉·格鲁博海姆
大型艺术品经销商。
Your painting is a work
of sheer genius!
你的画是一件作品
纯粹的天才！
I'll buy it.
我会买它。
You recognize my genius?
你认识我的天才吗？
Well, if you like that,
好吧，如果你喜欢的话，
you're gonna love
my other paintings.
你会喜欢的
我的其他画作。
Oh no, dear. Ew.
哦不，亲爱的。呃。
Those lack the spark of...
那些缺乏...的火花
this painting.
这幅画。
Oh.
哦。
Clearly, that little urchin
is your muse.
分明是那个小顽童
是你的缪斯。
Make me more paintings of him,
给我多画一些他的画
and I'll give you a show
in my gallery!
我会给你表演
在我的画廊里！
Here's my card.
这是我的名片。
Wow! She actually liked
your painting, Squidward.
哇！她其实喜欢
你的画，章鱼哥。
Yeah, what's wrong with her?
是啊，她怎么了？
My own gallery show.
我自己的画廊展览。
Soon, the whole world
will know me
很快，整个世界
会认识我
for my artistic soul, my genius.
为了我的艺术灵魂，我的天才。
Ugh!
But I gotta paint SpongeBob.
啊!
但我得画海绵宝宝。
I don't even like being
in the same ocean with him.
我什至不喜欢成为
与他在同一片海洋。
I can't ask him to pose for me.
我不能要求他给我摆姿势。
Wait. I'm a genius.
等待。我是个天才。
I'll just paint him from memory.
我就凭记忆画他吧。
Ah.
啊。
Oh.
哦。
Ugh! I've spent so long
啊!我花了这么久
trying to forget
SpongeBob exists,
试图忘记
海绵宝宝存在，
I've forgotten
what he looks like.
我忘记了
他长什么样。
There's only one thing to do.
只有一件事要做。
Stealth painting.
隐形画。
Woo-hoo-hoo!
呜呜呜！
Hm? Fries are ready!
嗯？薯条准备好了！
Ew. Those fries are off.
呃。那些薯条没了。
I better change
this boiling hot oil.
我最好改变一下
这沸腾的热油。
Aw, quittin' time.
噢，该辞职了。
Off to boating school.
去划船学校。
I'm coming, Mrs. Puff!
我来了，泡芙女士！
I need a more direct approach.
我需要一种更直接的方法。
Huh?
啊？
Oh.
哦。
Oh!
哦！
Whoop!
哎哟！
If fine arts aren't working,
如果美术不起作用
maybe martial arts will.
也许武术会。
Oh!
哦！
Ow!
噢！
Oh!
哦！
Hey! Them's my kids!
嘿！他们是我的孩子！
You-you don't understand.
你-你不明白。
But-but...
但是-但是...
Time for an even more
direct approach.
是时候更多了
直接方法。
♪ La-la-la-la-la-la-la
La-la-la-la ♪
♪ 啦啦啦啦啦啦啦啦
啦啦啦啦♪
SpongeBob.
海绵宝宝。
Oh, hello, Squidward--
哦，你好，章鱼哥——
Gotcha!
明白了！
Ah, you've done it again!
啊，你又这么做了！
Another beautiful masterpiece!
又一个美丽的杰作！
Just keep working
with your muse.
继续工作
与你的缪斯。
Yes, ma'am.
是的，女士。
I'm your muse?
我是你的缪斯？
Don't let it go to your head.
不要让它冲昏头脑。
Well, if you wanted me
to pose, Squidward,
好吧，如果你想要我
摆出姿势，章鱼哥，
all you had to do was ask.
您所要做的就是询问。
I would do anything
我愿意做任何事
to help you achieve
your artistic dreams.
帮助您实现
你的艺术梦想。
You would?
你会吗？
Of course.
当然。
Now let's get painting!
现在让我们开始画画吧！
I'm musing!
我在沉思！
♪ I'm musing
I'm musing, I'm musing ♪
♪ 我在沉思
我在沉思，我在沉思♪
Stand up there.
站起来。
Now, put one hand on your hip,
现在，将一只手放在臀部上，
and raise the other in the air.
并将另一个举到空中。
Got it!
知道了！
What do you think
about this pose?
你觉得怎么样
关于这个姿势？
Just pick a pose and stay still!
只需选择一个姿势并保持静止即可！
Yoo-hoo!
哟吼！
How about this?
这个怎么样？
I said stay still!
我说别动！
Thank you.
谢谢。
You haven't quite captured
my quality of mature naivete.
你还没有完全捕捉到
我的品质成熟天真。
You're supposed to be my muse,
not my critic.
你应该是我的缪斯
不是我的批评者。
Now I can paint.
现在我可以画画了。
Uh, SpongeBob?
呃，海绵宝宝？
Could you scoot forward?
你能向前冲吗？
You got it, Squidward!
你明白了，章鱼哥！
Oops, that wasn't me.
哎呀，那不是我。
That was the chair.
那是椅子。
SpongeBob, please stay still.
海绵宝宝，请保持安静。
Somebody step on a duck?
有人踩鸭子吗？
I can't take it anymore!
我再也受不了了！
Uh-oh. I guess Squidward
didn't find me amusing.
呃哦。我猜章鱼哥
没觉得我有趣。
Huh?
啊？
The way out!
出路！
- Paint the muse!
- 画出缪斯女神！
Paint the muse!
画出缪斯女神！
Yeah, Squidward! Paint me!
是啊，章鱼哥！画我吧！
Forever and ever and ever
and ever!
永远永远永远
永远！
Huh?
啊？
Oh, I'll paint you.
哦，我画你。
I'll paint you to oblivion!
我要把你画到遗忘！
♪ Here I go a-painting ♪
♪ 我来画画了 ♪
♪ A-painting, a-painting ♪
♪ 画，画 ♪
♪ Here I go a-painting ♪
♪ 我来画画了 ♪
♪ All the ding-dong day! ♪
♪ 叮咚的一天！ ♪
Time to make Squidward rich...
是时候让章鱼哥变得富有了……
and me richer!
而我更富有了！
Oh, dear.
哦亲爱的。
Looks like I pushed
another artist too hard.
看来是我推的
另一位艺术家太难了。
Mark up the prices
of his old paintings.
标记价格
他的旧画作。
I may have lost all my fame...
我可能已经失去了所有的名声......
...and money,
...还有金钱，
but at least,
I enjoy painting again.
但至少，
我又开始喜欢画画了。
Ow!
噢！
Hey, buddy,
you finished with that?
嘿，伙计，
你说完了吗？
- Yes.
- Great!
- 是的。
- 伟大的！
More garbage.
更多垃圾。
Typical.
典型的。